hollandresidential.com 2019-01-27

# Holland Residential | Privacy Policy

We collect from you only the personal information you voluntarily provide in order to deliver the best possible service. If you choose to process an online payment or reservation we ask you to provide us with information necessary to process your order which may include, but not be limited to, name, physical address, telephone number, facsimile number, email address, company name, title, credit card number, and expiration date. The credit card information that is collected is used strictly for billing purposes.

We collect your email address so we can send you information about your transaction and its status. We may use your email address to inform you about current offers or events from Holland Residential or its properties under management. We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law.

### **Sharing Your Personal Information**

Holland Residential does not sell information to unrelated third parties. Holland Residential does send your contact and order information to the facility that you selected for purposes of completing your payment or reservation.

### **Changes to This Online Privacy Policy**

Holland Residential reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Online Privacy Policy at any time. Accordingly, Holland Residential recommends that you revisit this Online Privacy Policy from time to time to ensure that you are aware of the current privacy practices. Your continued use of the web site following any changes signifies your acceptance of these changes.

### **Holland Residential and Session Cookies**

The Holland Residential web site uses session cookies to enable making transactions on our site. A session cookie is a small file placed on your computer which acts as a unique identifier to keep track of the information you have entered. Without the session cookie, our site cannot track the information you are entering, and you will be unable to complete your transaction.

A session cookie does not remain on your machine after you close your web browser window. Our session cookie contains none of your personal information, and cannot be used to track you around the web. It can only be used by our web site to identify the information you have entered during the transaction process which is required to complete the transaction.

### **How to Enable Cookies on your Browser**

Your web browser is the primary way you can control cookies.

The method for changing your cookie settings will vary depending on the browser you use, but options should be similar regardless of your browser choice.

### **Internet Explorer**

If you are using Internet Explorer, your cookies will be automatically controlled based on your privacy settings. If you would like to override automatic cookie control, choose Tools -> Internet Options -> Privacy -> Advanced. From this panel you can choose to override automatic cookie handling, and specify how you would like to deal with First Party and Third Party cookies.

First party cookies come from the owner of the website you are visiting, third party cookies come from a different company (for instance, an advertising company). You can select "Accept", "Block", or "Prompt" - if you choose "Prompt", your browser will notify you each time a web site attempts to set a cookie on your machine, and you can choose to accept or reject the cookie. If you would like to accept session cookies, but not persistent cookies, check the box to "Always Allow Session Cookies." Please note that session cookies are required to enable shopping on many web sites.

### **Firefox**

Cookie options are available at Tools -> Options -> Privacy -> Cookies.

### **Chrome**

Cookie options are available under Tools -> Options -> Under the Hood -> Content Settings -> Cookies.

### **Safari**

Cookie options are available under Safari -> Preferences -> Security.

Other web browsers provide similar options. Alternatively, you can also control cookies with a number of internet security packages. If you use one of these packages, please refer to the software documentation for more information.

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses Cookies. The information generated by the Cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. [Find Google's privacy policy here.](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)
